Beginning tonight at 2 a.m., Chicago is going to see the largest military presence in the entire history of Chicago.
Beginning tonight at 2 a.m., the critters will be crawling their way through Little Village,
and they will be wreaking havoc door-to-door, dragging people out of their homes,
and placing them into custody to get them ready for processing and deportation.
So I'm letting the public know right now, prepare, get ready for a civilian showdown.
I'm done calling it a music festival. This is a civilian showdown.
We all need to participate in protecting and defending the lives of innocent people.
This is what I have been working so hard to protect and prepare people for.
Unfortunately, we are at a point now where the time has come to do everything in our power,
and this is the steps we have to take.
If you have kids, please get them out of Little Village.
If you have pets, please get them out of Little Village.
And all the surrounding areas and neighborhoods within Little Village.
Humble Park, you are at risk.
Little Village, you are at risk.
Boys Town, you are at risk.
Internal Services and all of my intelligence is asking you to prepare for a civil showdown,
because what is happening now is a complete overreach of the United States government.
The Critters have already began mobilizing in Chicago, and they've been doing this for quite some time now.
If you see a drone, you are asked to destroy it.
Plain and simple. Destroy it.
And if you are met with deadly force, I'm telling you right now,
do everything in your power to protect your life,
and don't take it for granted.
Take your phone. Make sure your phone is fully charged before you get out of your house.
Take more than one person with you.
If you plan to go outside and leave your home to run errands,
go in groups. Go in large groups.
Large groups.
Bring more than one person with you.
Do not go out of your house by yourself.
And if you are a street vendor in Little Village,
you are being asked to remain in your home.
Don't go to public parks.
I love you all.
Stay safe out there.